<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SprooktochtApp</string>
    <string name="voer_uw_naam_in">Enter your name</string>
    <string name="sprookje_details_foto">Fairytale Details picture</string>
    <string name="voer_hier_sprookjes_info_in">Input fairytale info here</string>
    <string name="sprookjes_details">Fairytae details</string>
    <string name="sprookjes_naam">name Fairytale</string>
    <string name="placeholder_tutorial_text">Placeholder tutorial text</string>
    <string name="ga_naar">Go to:</string>
    <string name="activesprookje">ActiveFairytale</string>
    <string name="voortgang">Progression:</string>
    <string name="plattegrond">Minimap</string>
    <string name="drieBiggetjesTitel">The three little piglets</string>
    <string name="drieBiggetjesHulp">The three little pigs need your help. They have all built a house and would like to know how strong each house is. There seems to be a big bad wolf nearby and the piglets would rather not end up in the wolf\'s stomach. Can you blow down all the houses?</string>
    <string name="drieBiggetjesOpdracht">The 3 little pigs have all built their own house to protect themselves against the big bad wolf, but they are not sure whether their houses are all sturdy enough. Can you see if you can blow them over by blowing into the big fan?</string>
    <string name="drieBiggetjes">Once upon a time there were three little pigs, all on an adventure in the big world. They were brothers and each of them planned to build a house. The youngest piglet was lazy and built his house of straw. The eldest was very enthusiastic and built his house of stone. The middle one thinks it\'s a good idea to make his house out of wood. But one day a wolf came and was only too happy to have a nice piglet for breakfast. He arrived at the cottage made of straw and blew it like that. The youngest piglet got away and ran as fast as he could to his brother. The wolf ran after it and once he got to the wooden house, he took a deep breath and blew down that little house too. The piglets had no other choice and ran to their eldest brother, hoping to be safe there. The wolf didn\'t want to lose the piglets so went after them on an empty stomach. When the wolf arrived at the stone house, he took another deep breath and blew against the house with full force. But to his surprise, the house did not fall over. He blew again but the house was still standing. The wolf did not give up even though the three little pigs had already escaped. What happened to the house in the end is another story.</string>
    <string name="hansEnGrietjeTitel">Hansel and Gretel</string>
    <string name="hansEnGrietjeHulp">Hansel and Gretel are lost and at the moment are standing in front of a huge house of cookies, sweets and so on. They are only too eager to eat some of those candies, but they also see that the witch is there watching them. You can help them get a full stomach by grabbing as many candies as possible when the witch isn\'t paying attention.</string>
    <string name="hansEnGrietjeOpdracht">Help Hansel and Gretel to a full stomach by pressing the buttons on the candies that the witch is not looking at. When the witch is looking at a candy, the light hanging above it will light up. Can you eat the whole house?</string>
    <string name="hansEnGrietje">Er was eens een verhaal over een gezin dat best arm was. Het ging over Hans en Grietje die samen met hun ouders in een oud huisje leefden. Uiteindelijk besloten de ouders dat Hans en Grietje eten moesten gaan halen. Hans had door dat het moeilijk was de weg terug te vinden en nam daarom kiezelstenen mee om een pad te vormen uitkwam bij thuis. De volgende dag wilde Hans hetzelfde doen, maar hij gebruikte dit keer broodkruimels in plaats van kiezelstenen. Toen ze weer naar huis wilden, kwamen ze erachter dat alle broodkruimels opgegeten waren. Grietje zei dat ze maar moesten ronddwalen, want stil blijven staan is ook geen optie. Na een tijdje in het bos te lopen, zien ze een huisje van koek, snoep en nog meer lekkers. Ze konden zich niet inhouden en aten van het huisje, maar toen kwam er iemand uit de voordeur lopen. Het was een oude vrouw die aardig over kwam en een slaapplek aanbood voor de twee kinderen. Na een volle maag en een goede nachtrust bleek de oude vrouw een heks te zijn en Hans was opgesloten in een kooi. De heks was van plan om Hans te vet mesten maar Hans liet elke keer een botje in plaats van zijn vinger zien, omdat de heks slecht ziend was. Na een paar dagen was de Heks er klaar mee en moest Grietje het water opwarmen om hans in de soep te gooien. Maar Grietje deed net alsof ze niet wist hoe de oven werkte dus toen de heks kwam kijken duwde grietje de heks in de oven. Daarna bevrijdde ze Hans en namen goud en sieraden van de heks mee. Toen ze weer thuiskwamen waren de ouders heel erg blij en ze hoeven nooit meer in armoede te leven.</string>
    <string name="tutorial1">Welcome to the Fairytale Tour! In this app you will go on an adventure through the Essteling to help all the characters. Collect points along the way to be able to win a nice prize. Will you be able to help all the characters in the park?</string>
    <string name="tutorial2">You will soon be at the game itself, here you can do several things. There are different buttons on the minimap, which are the different puzzles that you have to solve. If you press the button and then press more info you can go to a screen where the problem is explained.</string>
    <string name="tutorial3">Above the map there is a trophy. When you have collected enough points you can press this trophy to collect your prize! You can choose from a free snack with your fries, a 20% discount at the souvenir shop or you can skip the line at 1 attraction.</string>
    <string name="tutorial4">There is also a button with a question mark, you can press this button if you don\'t understand something, then you come back to this tutorial. If it\'s still not clear, ask one of the park employees for help!</string>
    <string name="tutorial5">Once you have arrived at the game there is a code that you have to enter in your phone. Once you have done this, you can press the start button and you will receive an explanation of your assignment. Complete the assignment as well as possible and earn as many points as possible!</string>
    <string name="tutorial6">There are different levels of difficulty in each game, the harder the level, the more points you can earn! When you finish the game you will get all the points you have earned on your phone, collect as many points as possible to win cool prizes!</string>
    <string name="wolfEnBiggetjes">The three little piglets</string>
    <string name="skip">skip</string>
    <string name="go">continue</string>
</resources>